Guide to the Frances Hesselbein Papers, 1942-2013 AIS.2013.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Frances Hesselbein Personal Papers, ca. 1930s-1940s, 1955-2014; B.
  - Audio/Visual Material, 1930s-1940s, 1978-2013, undated; IX.
    - Girl Scouts of the United States of America, 1978-1998, 2011; 1.
      - Peter F. Drucker Seminar for GSUSA - Peter Drucker's Concluding Remarks, April 1989 (Box 43, Cassette 3)
      - National Agency Prof. Award - Hesselbein/Girl Scouts Award, 1985 (Box 43, Disk 1)
      - Peter Drucker pre-dinner speech - 1998 Drucker Conference/National Meeting of Girl Scout Council Executive Directors Peter Drucker presentation excerpt, September 1989, 1998 (Box 43, Disk 2)
      - A Membership Message from Frances Hesselbein/A Tribute to Frances Hesselbein - "Paths that Cross", 1989-1990 (Box 43, Disk 3)
      - Paths That Cross: A Tribute to Frances Hesselbein, January 1990 (Box 43, Disk 4)
      - Arizona Cactus-Pine Council - A Personal Message to Frances Hesselbein, undated (Box 43, Disk 5)
      - GSUSA Convention pictures, 2011 (Box 43, Disk 6)
      - WAGGGS 25th Conference photo slides, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Peter Drucker event with the Girl Scouts photo slides, 1980s (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Girl Scout Africa and Greece trip photo slides, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Girl Scout event photo slides, November 1987 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Personal, 1930s-1940s, 1985-2013, undated; 2.
      - Adventure in Excellence Symposium - Mutual Adventure, April 6, 1991 (Box 44, Video 1)
      - Frances Hesselbein speech - Chevron Texaco Management Institute, October 5, 2004 (Box 44, Video 2)
      - Texaco Management Institute Spanish version - Frances Hesselbein, 1990s-2000s (Box 44, Video 3)
      - Frances Hesselbein United Way award, 1985 (Box 44, Video 4)
      - "Frances at Harvard", March 1990 (Box 44, Video 5)
      - 2nd Work Redesign Symposium - The Pyramid and the Web, February 1991 (Box 44, Video 6)
      - The Pennsylvania Society Dinner, 1991 (Box 44, Video 7)
      - Frances Hesselbein interview with Alan Campbell, March 1992 (Box 44, Video 8)
      - Frances Hesselbein - College Board Speaker Series, September 8, 1994 (Box 44, Video 9)
      - Empire Club - Frances Hesselbein, October 26, 1995 (Box 44, Video 10)
      - Hewlett-Packard TWC - CEO Panel Discussion, 1995 (Box 44, Video 11)
      - "Beyond the Walls: New Partnership for a New World" - MAQIN Hunter Conference, May 1997 (Box 44, Video 12)
      - Frances Hesselbein - Fulani! appearances, 1997 (Box 44, Video 13)
      - Medal of Freedom presentation, January 15, 1998 (Box 44, Video 14)
      - Lutheran Services in America conference keynote speech, April 23, 1998 (Box 44, Video 15)
      - Civilian Leadership Symposium panel - "OPD", December 12, 1999 (Box 44, Video 16)
      - Arizona State University Capstone dinner speech, November 13, 2001 (Box 44, Video 17)
      - FedEx Leadership Series - "What Works: Leadership from the Boardroom to the Front Line", January 2002 (Box 44, Video 18)
      - Dwight D. Eisenhower National Security Conference summary video, 2002 (Box 44, Video 19)
      - Leadership Forum with Frances Hesselbein - Reel 1 Close-ups, May 20, 2003 (Box 44, Video 20)
      - Leadership Forum with Frances Hesselbein - Reel 2 Close-ups, May 20, 2003 (Box 44, Video 21)
      - Leadership Forum with Frances Hesselbein - Reel 3 Close-ups, May 20, 2003 (Box 44, Video 22)
      - Leadership Forum with Frances Hesselbein - Reel 1 Wide shots, May 20, 2003 (Box 44, Video 23)
      - U of T/Leadership Forum - "Lessons of Experience for the Leader of the Future", May 21, 2003 (Box 44, Video 24)
      - The Pennsylvania Society dinner, 2003 (Box 44, Video 25)
      - CADCA morning plenary, January 21, 2004 (Box 44, Video 26)
      - Chevron Texaco Management Institute speech, October 5, 2004 (Box 44, Video 27)
      - Fordham University Graduate School of Education - An Invitation to the 7th Annual National Principals' Leadership Institute, undated (Box 44, Video 28)
      - Hewlett-Packard WTC Tape #3 - Hesselbein window dub, undated (Box 44, Video 29)
      - "Soldier, Come Home" by Frank Wicks, undated (Box 44, Video 30)
      - Frances Hesselbein - Chevron-Texaco speech, September 24, 2004 (Box 44, Video 31)
      - Drucker on Innovation - Interview with Frances Hesselbein, 1986 (Box 44, Cassette 1)
      - Chautauqua Institution Lecture Series - Frances Hesselbein, 1993 (Box 44, Cassette 2)
      - Planning Forum - The ISM Conference Keynote presentation, 1994 (Box 44, Cassette 3)
      - VNAA's 10th Annual Meeting - Spotlight on Leadership Keynote address, undated (Box 44, Cassette 4)
      - Tape #2 - Positioning Yourself to Make a Difference, undated (Box 44, Cassette 5)
      - Frances Hesselbein speech dictation, undated (Box 44, Cassette 6)
      - "Ohio speech" notes recording, undated (Box 44, Cassette 7)
      - Frances Hesselbein dictating management reports/memos to colleagues, undated (Box 44, Cassette 8)
      - The Best of Executive Coaching, 2010 (Box 44, Disk 1)
      - Military Child Education Coalition and the Frances Hesselbein Student Leadership Program, October - November 2011 (Box 44, Disk 2)
      - Success - Achiever's Pack Book summaries and audio series, 2012 (Box 44, Disk 3)
      - Military Child Education Coalition and the Frances Hesselbein Student Leadership Program, April 2013 (Box 44, Disk 4)
      - Military Child Education Coalition and the Frances Hesselbein Student Leadership Program, October-November 2013 (Box 44, Disk 5)
      - Mentor Gallery - Gonzaga University, 1990s-2000s (Box 44, Disk 6)
      - Songs of Inspiration for Frances, 2000s (Box 44, Disk 7)
      - John Hesselbein manuscript, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Pennsylvania Society dinner photos, 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Personal photographs, ca. 1930s - 2010s (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Canadian Society of Association Executives conference - Hesselbein speech, 1996 (Box 45, Disk 1)
      - Frances Hesselbein/Tom Peters - Leader Talk! with Garrison Krause, 1998 (Box 45, Disk 2)
      - Eisenhower Award for Mrs. Frances Hesselbein - Eisenhower National Security Series, 1990s-2000s (Box 45, Disk 3)
      - Frances Hesselbein speech to be delivered - Tempe, Arizona, November 13, 2001 (Box 45, Disk 4)
      - Jim Collins and Frances Hesselbein - Living Leadership, October 20, 2004 (Box 45, Disk 5)
      - Frances Hesselbein - National Corp Leadership Meeting, 2004 (Box 45, Disk 6)
      - Professor Rao and Frances Hesselbein - Columbia University School of Business, April 1, 2005 (Box 45, Disk 7)
      - The Trust Factor: Leadership in an Age of Cynicism - Hesselbein speech, April 7, 2005 (Box 45, Disk 8)
      - 60th Anniversary of Korean Independence Day message, June 2005 (Box 45, Disk 9)
      - Hesselbein Keynote speech at Duke University, October 19, 2006 (Box 45, Disk 10)
      - Frances Hesselbein interview, October 2006 (Box 45, Disk 11)
      - NYCLC - The Power of intentional Leadership: Q and A Session, September 20, 2008 (Box 45, Disk 12)
      - NYCLC - The Power of Intentional Leadership: Frances Hesselbein and Harry Tucker, September 20, 2008 (Box 45, Disk 13)
      - NYCLC Launch dinner - Frances Hesselbein and W. Wilson Goode, September 2008 (Box 45, Disk 14)
      - Jim Collins introduces Frances Hesselbein - Drucker on Innovation San Diego, 2009 (Box 45, Disk 15)
      - Hesselbein Global Academy for Student Leadership and Civic Engagement, July 13, 2009 (Box 45, Disk 16)
      - Remarks for Peter Drucker 100th Birthday Celebration, 2009 (Box 45, Disk 17)
      - Consuelo Mack - Wealthtrack, December 24, 2010 (Box 45, Disk 18)
      - National Character and Leadership Symposium, 2010 (Box 45, Disk 19)
      - Indiana University Oral History Project - Hesselbein interviews, 2011 (Box 45, Disk 20)
      - Third Annual Summit of the Hesselbein Global Academy for Student Leadership and Civic Engagement - Warren Bennis and Frances Hesselbein, 2011 (Box 46, Disk 1)
      - Frances Hesselbein at GSUSA HQ, August 9, 2011 (Box 46, Disk 2)
      - Richard Hefner's Open Mind - In Search of Leadership, January 19, 2012 (Box 46, Disk 3)
      - One to One with Sheryl McCarthy - Frances Hesselbein guest appearance, April 16, 2012 (Box 46, Disk 4)
      - Peace through Commerce - Frances Hesselbein and Rev. Oliver Williams, April 24, 2012 (Box 46, Disk 5)
      - Jim Collins on Frances Hesselbein, 2000s (Box 46, Disk 6)
      - AARP - Frances Hesselbein presentation, undated (Box 46, Disk 7)
      - Frances clips from Leadership Dialogues, undated (Box 46, Disk 8)
      - Frances Hesselbein Leadership Dialogues, undated (Box 46, Disk 9)
      - Frances Hesselbein - To Serve is to Live, undated (Box 46, Disk 10)
      - Leadership Forum with Frances Hesselbein - Reels 1-3, undated (Box 46, Disk 11)
      - Meet the Gurus - Frances Hesselbein, undated (Box 46, Disk 9)
      - Texaco Management Institute ft. Frances Hesselbein, undated (Box 46, Disk 10)
      - Girl Scout photos, 1980s (Box 47, Disk 1)
      - CADCA photos, October 14, 2004 (Box 47, Disk 2)
      - Frances Hesselbein at Agora - Melbourne Citymission, 2004 (Box 47, Disk 3)
      - Frances Hesselbein and Jim Warner, 2005 (Box 47, Disk 4)
      - American Red Cross Cabaret and Cuisine - Frances Hesselbein reception, April 7, 2006 (Box 47, Disk 5)
      - XVIII Airborne Corps Strategic Leadership Day, October 19, 2007 (Box 47, Disk 6)
      - Joshua MacLeod photo of Frances Hesselbein, 2008 (Box 47, Disk 7)
      - Celebrating Frances reception, November 1, 2010 (Box 47, Disk 8)
      - United States Air Force Academy visit, 2010 (Box 47, Disk 9)
      - United States Air Force Academy visit pt. 2, 2010 (Box 47, Disk 10)
      - Book signing photos at GSUSA, August 9, 2011 (Box 47, Disk 11)
      - Frances on Cape Cod, September 2011 (Box 47, Disk 12)
      - Frances Hesselbein Book Signing, December 14, 2011 (Box 47, Disk 13)
      - Frances Hesselbein Historical visit to Cape Cod, 2012 (Box 47, Disk 14)
      - Frances R. Hesselbein - Mak. Lunch, 2013 (Box 47, Disk 15)
      - Investment in America Forum Day 1 CD 1, undated (Box 47, Disk 16)
      - Investment in America Forum Day 1 CD 2, undated (Box 47, Disk 17)
      - Investment in America Forum Day 1 CD 3, undated (Box 47, Disk 18)
      - Investment in America Forum Day 2 CD 1, undated (Box 47, Disk 19)
      - Investment in America Forum Day 2 CD 2, undated (Box 47, Disk 20)
      - Personal photo negatives, undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Audio Cassette Tapes (Box 52)
      - Audio Cassette Tapes (Box 53)